Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 2: Legislative Committee Files. 1954-1994
    - Subseries 2: Appropriations. 1954-1994
      - Appropriations: Foreign Operations, 1976-1994
        - Costa Rica. 1983-1991 (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Cyprus. 1988-1994 (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Development Assistance. 1984 (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - Development Banks. 1983-1985 (Box 57, Folder 12)
        - Doctor Sherman, African Aid. 1994 (Box 57, Folder 13)
        - Drugs, Refugees, Terrorism. 1986 (Box 57, Folder 14)
        - East Timor. 1991-1994 (Box 57, Folder 15)
        - Eastern Europe. 1990 (Box 57, Folder 16)
        - Egypt. 1987-1991 (Box 57, Folder 17)
        - El Salvador. 1981-1994 (Box 57, Folder 18-20)
        - Enterprise for the Americas Institute. 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 21)
        - Esperanca. 1984-1994 (Box 57, Folder 22)
        - Ethiopia. 1983-1988 (Box 57, Folder 23)
        - Ethiopia. 1985 (Box 57, Folder 24)
        - Ethiopia (Operation Moses). 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 25)
        - Ethiopian Jewry. 1984-1991 (Box 57, Folder 26)
        - Family Planning. 1975-1985 (Box 57, Folder 27)
        - Family Planning. 1986-1990 (Box 57, Folder 28)
        - Father D'Agostino. 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 29)
        - Foreign Assistance. 1986 (Box 57, Folder 30)
        - Foreign Assistance. 1986 (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - Foreign Assistance 1978-1988 (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - Foreign Assistance. 1995 (Box 58, Folder 3-6)
        - Foreign Assistance Authorization. 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Foreign Assistance, Background and Correspondence. 1977-1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - Foreign Assistance Conference. 1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Foreign Assistance (Human Rights). 1977 (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - Foreign Investment in the United States. 1979-1981 (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - Foreign Relations Authorization. 1981 (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - Foundation for International Community Assistance. 1987 (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - General. 1977-1994 (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - Global Exchange and Agency for International Development. 1986-1988 (Box 58, Folder 15)
        - Global Poverty Education Act. 1988-1989 (Box 58, Folder 16)
        - Greece and Cyprus. 1984-1994 (Box 58, Folder 17)
        - Greece and Turkey. 1987 (Box 58, Folder 18)
        - Guarantee Reserve Fund. 1987 (Box 58, Folder 19)
        - Gulf Cooperation Council. 1988 (Box 58, Folder 20)
        - Gulf War. 1991 (Box 58, Folder 21)
        - Gutherie Latex. 1994 (Box 58, Folder 22)
        - H.R. 4426 Fiscal Year 1995 Appropriations. 1994 (Box 58, Folder 23)
        - Haiti. 1985-1992 (Box 58, Folder 24)
        - Hearing on the New Independent States of Russia. 1994 (Box 58, Folder 25)
        - Hearings. 1991 (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Hearings, Atwood. 1994 (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - Honduras. 1987-1991 (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - Hostages. 1981-1992 (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - Human Rights Hearing. 1994 (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - Iodine Deficiencies. 1991 (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - India. 1989-1992 (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - Indonesia. 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - International Arid Lands Consortium. 1994 (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - International Conference on Assistance to Refugees in Africa. 1984-1986 (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - International Development. 1989-1990 (Box 59, Folder 11)
        - International Development Assistance Act. 1979-1980 (Box 59, Folder 12)
        - International Fund for Agricultural Development. 1985 (Box 59, Folder 13)
        - International Monetary Fund. 1983 (Box 59, Folder 14)
        - International Narcotics Control. 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 15)
        - International Narcotics Matters. 1992-1993 (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - International Refugee Assistance. 1985 (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - International Security Assistance Hearing. 1994 (Box 59, Folder 18)
        - Iraqi Refugees. 1984-1991 (Box 59, Folder 19)
        - Ireland. 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 20)
        - Israel. 1980-1994 (Box 59, Folder 21-22)
        - Israel Assistance. 1989-1992 (Box 59, Folder 23)
        - Israeli Loan Guarantees. 1992 (Box 59, Folder 24)
        - Italy. 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 25)
        - Jordan. 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 26)
        - Jordan Arms Sales. 1982-1986 (Box 59, Folder 27)
        - Jordan Arms Sales v. Israel's Security. 1985 (Box 59, Folder 28)
        - Kenya. 1991-1993 (Box 59, Folder 29)
        - Kissinger Commission. 1984 (Box 59, Folder 30)
        - Kuwait F-18 Sale. 1988 (Box 59, Folder 31)
        - Kuwait and Iraq. 1989-1992 (Box 59, Folder 32)
        - Lebanon. 1982-1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - Liberia. 1984-1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - Macedonia. 1993-1994 (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - Medical Development for Israel. 1991-1992 (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - Mexico. 1985-1988 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
        - Mexico City Policy (Family Planning). 1987 (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - Microenterprise. 1986-1993 (Box 60, Folder 8-11)
        - Middle East. 1986-1992 (Box 60, Folder 12-13)
        - Middle East Fact Finding Mission. 1983 (Box 60, Folder 14)
        - Middle East Report (Codel). 1983 (Box 60, Folder 15)
        - Missile Sales. 1988-1990 (Box 60, Folder 16)
        - Mozambique. 1987-1988 (Box 60, Folder 17)
        - Multilateral Development Banks. 1984-1994 (Box 60, Folder 18)
        - Multilateral Economic Assistance. 1987-1994 (Box 60, Folder 19)
        - Namibia. 1983-1991 (Box 60, Folder 20)
        - National Endowment for Democracy. 1983-1993 (Box 60, Folder 21)
        - National Law Center for Free Trade. 1992-1994 (Box 60, Folder 22)
        - National University (Costa Rica). 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - Natural Family Planning. 1977-1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - Nicaragua Election. 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 3-4)
        - Nicaraguan Contra Aid. 1985-1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - Overseas Private Investment Corporation. 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - Pakistan. 1987-1995 (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - Pakistani Overthrow of Elections. 1990 (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - Palestine Liberation Organization. 1989-1995 (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - Panama. 1987-1990 (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - Peace Corps. 1985-1988 (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - Peace Now. 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 12)
        - Philippines. 1985-1990 (Box 61, Folder 13)
        - Poland. 1989-1994 (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - Poland and Hungary. 1989 (Box 61, Folder 15)
        - Private Voluntary Organizations. 1985 (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - Qatar. 1988-1990 (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - Questions. 1989 (Box 61, Folder 18)
        - Radio Free Europe. 1987-1993 (Box 61, Folder 19)
        - Refugee Assistance. 1985-1988 (Box 61, Folder 20)
        - Requests. 1992-1994 (Box 61, Folder 21-24)
        - Response to Letters on Foreign Investments and Aid. no date (Box 61, Folder 25)
        - Results Organization. 1993 (Box 61, Folder 26)
        - Russia Aid. 1993-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - Russian Refugees. 1990-1991 (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - Saudi Arabia Arms Sales. 1978-1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - Saudi Arabia Arms Sales Hearing. 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - Security Assistance. 1986 (Box 62, Folder 5)
        - Senate Hearings: Foreign Assistance FY 1988. 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6-8)
        - Senate Hearings: Foreign Assistance FY 1989. 1989 (Box 62, Folder 9-13)
        - Shaare Zedek Medical Center, Jerusalem. 1986-1988 (Box 62, Folder 14)
        - Shultz. 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 15)
        - Sister Cities. 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 16)
        - South Africa. 1985-1989 (Box 62, Folder 17)
        - South African Sanctions. 1990-1994 (Box 62, Folder 18)
        - Soviet Union. 1990-1993 (Box 62, Folder 19)
        - Soviet United Loans. 1985-1987 (Box 62, Folder 20)
        - Sri Lanka Aid (Human Rights). 1983-1986 (Box 62, Folder 21)
        - Stinger Missile Amendment. 1982-1987 (Box 62, Folder 22)
        - Stinger Missiles. 1986-1987 (Box 62, Folder 23)
        - Sudan. 1984-1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Supplemental Assistance. 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Supplemental, Bahrain. 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Support for Eastern European Democracy. 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Taiwan. 1989-1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Tel Aviv Museum. 1987-1988 (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Turkey. 1987-1994 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Turkish Aid Letters. 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 8)
        - Ukraine. 1980-1994 (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - United Nations. 1982-1994 (Box 63, Folder 10)
        - United Nations Children's Fund. 1982-1990 (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - United Nations Population Fund. 1989-1994 (Box 63, Folder 12)
        - United Nations Sudano-Sahelian Office. 1986-1987 (Box 63, Folder 13)
        - United States Academy of Peace. 1981-1985 (Box 63, Folder 14)
        - U.S. Agency for International Development. 1994 (Box 63, Folder 15)
        - United States Information Agency. 1984-1986 (Box 63, Folder 16)
        - Universal Immunization. 1985-1991 (Box 63, Folder 17)
        - Vietnam Amputees. 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 18)
        - Volunteer Business Counselors: The Service Corps of Retired Executives Association. 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 19)
        - Voting Records. 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 20)
        - Women in Development. 1986-1988 (Box 63, Folder 21)
        - World Bank. 1980-1994 (Box 63, Folder 22)
        - World Hunger. 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 23)
        - Zaire. 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 24)
      - Appropriations: General, 1975-1994
        - Act H.R. 4800. 1988 (Box 63, Folder 25)
        - Agency Buck Responses. 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 26)
        - Agency Buck Responses. 1986 (Box 63, Folder 27)
        - Agency Buck Responses. 1987 (Box 63, Folder 28-29)
        - Amendments to Continuing Resolution Fiscal Year 1987. 1986 (Box 63, Folder 30)
        - Appropriations Achievements. 1990 (Box 63, Folder 31)
        - Appropriations Achievements. 1991 (Box 63, Folder 32)
        - Bill Status. 1977-1989 (Box 63, Folder 33)
        - Briefing Book Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 63, Folder 34-36)
        - Briefing Book Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 63, Folder 37-38)
        - Briefing Book Fiscal Year 1995. 1994 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Buck Responses: Education. 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - Buck Responses: Labor. 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Buck Responses: Miscellaneous Agencies. 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - Buck Responses: Social Services. 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - Budget Reconciliation FY 1991. 1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - Budget Requests FY 1982. 1982 (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Budget Estimates (Book). 1975-1977 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Budget Estimates (Book). 1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - Chairman's Responses to DDC Appropriations Requests. 1993 (Box 64, Folder 10)
        - Committee Prints. 1988-1993 (Box 64, Folder 11)
        - Committee Votes. 1979 (Box 64, Folder 12)
        - Continuing Appropriations Report. 1987 (Box 64, Folder 13)
        - Continuing Resolution Fiscal Year 1986. 1985 (Box 64, Folder 14)
        - Continuing Resolution Fiscal Year 1987. 1986 (Box 64, Folder 15-16)
        - Correspondence. 1987-1988 (Box 64, Folder 17)
        - Correspondence: Constituents. 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence and Memos. 1977-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3-5)
        - Correspondence, Senators' Responses to DeConcini Requests. 1990-1993 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
        - Correspondence (Thank You's). 1984-1988 (Box 65, Folder 8-9)
        - Emergency Supplemental Appropriations. 1992-1993 (Box 65, Folder 10-11)
        - Grazing Fees. 1986 (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - Interior Committee. 1976-1993 (Box 65, Folder 13)
        - Legislative Request Letters. 1992 (Box 65, Folder 14)
        - Motor Vehicle Amendment to Reconciliation Bill. 1985 (Box 65, Folder 15)
        - Requests. 1993 (Box 65, Folder 16)
        - Requests Fiscal Year 1991. 1990 (Box 65, Folder 17)
        - Requests Fiscal Year 1992. 1991 (Box 65, Folder 18)
        - Requests Fiscal Year 1992-1995. 1991-1994 (Box 65, Folder 19)
        - Senator Byrd's Speeches. 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 20)
        - Supplemental Appropriations-Capitol Restoration. 1977-1983 (Box 65, Folder 21)
        - Supplemental Appropriations: Fiscal Year 1984. 1983 (Box 65, Folder 22-23)
        - Supplemental Appropriations: Fiscal Year 1985. 1985 (Box 65, Folder 24-25)
        - Supplemental Appropriations: Fiscal Year 1986. 1985-1986 (Box 65, Folder 26)
        - Supplemental Appropriations: Fiscal Year 1994. 1993 (Box 65, Folder 27)
        - Supplemental Appropriations HR 1127. 1987 (Box 65, Folder 28)
        - Supplemental Appropriations HR 2118. 1993 (Box 65, Folder 29)
        - Supplemental Appropriations HR 4515. 1986 (Box 65, Folder 30)
        - Supplemental Appropriations HR 1335 Emergency App. 1993 (Box 65, Folder 31)
        - Supplemental Appropriations-Jobs. 1983 (Box 65, Folder 32)
        - Supplemental Appropriations-Midwest. 1993 (Box 65, Folder 33)
        - Supplemental Appropriations-Pay and Honoraria. 1983 (Box 65, Folder 34)
        - Supplemental Appropriations Report. 1983 (Box 65, Folder 35)
        - Supplemental Appropriations, Spring 1987. 1987 (Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Supplemental Appropriations, Supporting Documents. 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Supplemental Appropriations, Udall Foundation. 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations: Interior & Related Agencies, 1976-1994
        - Animal Damage Control. 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 4)
        - Army Corps of Engineers Briefing Book. 1990 (Box 66, Folder 5-6)
        - Army Corps of Engineers: Gila River Indian Community. 1988 (Box 66, Folder 7)
        - Army Corps of Engineers: Holbrook Levees. 1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
        - Army Corps of Engineers: Reorganization Plan. 1993 (Box 66, Folder 9)
        - Army Corps of Engineers: Salt River Valley Flood Study. 1986 (Box 66, Folder 10)
        - Army Corps of Engineers: Tat Momlikot Dam. 1987-1988 (Box 66, Folder 11)
        - Arts and Humanities: Commission on Fine Arts. 1989 (Box 66, Folder 12)
        - Arts and Humanities: Martha Graham. 1982-1988 (Box 66, Folder 13)
        - Arts and Humanities: Hearing Material. 1990 (Box 66, Folder 14)
        - Arts and Humanities: National Assembly of State Arts Agencies. 1985 (Box 66, Folder 15)
        - Arts and Humanities: National Committee Arts. 1986 (Box 66, Folder 16)
        - Arts and Humanities: National Endowment for the Arts. 1977-1991 (Box 66, Folder 17-21)
        - Arts and Humanities: National Endowment for Children's Television. 1977-1979 (Box 66, Folder 22)
        - Arts and Humanities: National Endowment for the Humanities. 1978-1993 (Box 66, Folder 23-26)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Antigua Land Exchange. 1993 (Box 66, Folder 27)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona. 1994 (Box 66, Folder 28)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona Land Sales. 1983-1984 (Box 66, Folder 29)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona Mining Association. 1989 (Box 66, Folder 30)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona Mining Association. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 1-5)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona Strip. 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Arizona Wilderness Public Opinion. 1983 (Box 67, Folder 7)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Barry Goldwater Range. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 8)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Bibles Nomination. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 9)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Briefing Book. 1989-1993 (Box 67, Folder 10-12)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Budget. 1994 (Box 67, Folder 13)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Budget Justifications. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 14)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Budget Justifications FY 1990. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 15)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Buffalo Ridge. 1984-1985 (Box 67, Folder 16)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Bumblebee Exchange. 1987 (Box 67, Folder 17)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Burros. 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 18)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Colorado River Salinity. 1987-1989 (Box 67, Folder 19)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Correspondence. 1974-1980 (Box 67, Folder 20)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Correspondence. 1982-1988 (Box 67, Folder 21)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Correspondence. 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 22)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Empire Cienega Funding. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 23)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Ferguson Lake Cabin Sites. 1989 (Box 67, Folder 24)
        - Bureau of Land Management: General. 1989-1990 (Box 67, Folder 25)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Gray Ranch. 1993 (Box 67, Folder 26)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Grazing Fees. 1984-1991 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Hearing Materials. 1984-1992 (Box 68, Folder 4-7)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Hohokam Heritage Center. 1993 (Box 68, Folder 8)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Imperial Oasis (Yuma). 1993 (Box 68, Folder 9)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Interagency Agreement. 1988 (Box 68, Folder 10)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Klump Ranch. 1992 (Box 68, Folder 11)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Lake Havasu. 1993 (Box 68, Folder 12)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Mexican Border. 1993 (Box 68, Folder 13)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Migratory Bird Losses. 1989 (Box 68, Folder 14)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Mo Udall Park. 1989 (Box 68, Folder 15)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Old Yuma Mine. 1984 (Box 68, Folder 16)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Organic Act. 1976 (Box 68, Folder 17)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Payments in Lieu of Taxes. 1977-1989 (Box 68, Folder 18-19)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Phoenix District. 1989 (Box 68, Folder 20)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Phoenix District. 1992 (Box 68, Folder 21)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Pima County. 1986-1989 (Box 68, Folder 22)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Public Lands Advisory Council. 1984 (Box 68, Folder 23)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Red Rock, Del Webb. 1994 (Box 68, Folder 24)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Rights of Way. 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 25)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Safford. 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 26)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Safford Brinkerhoff. 1986-1992 (Box 68, Folder 27)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Safford District. 1984-1993 (Box 68, Folder 28)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Safford Resource. 1990 (Box 68, Folder 29)
        - Bureau of Land Management: San Pedro Conservation Area. 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 30)
        - Bureau of Land Management: San Pedro River. 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 31-32)
        - Bureau of Land Management: San Simon Valley Restoration. 1977-1980 (Box 68, Folder 33)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Santa Fe Split Estates. 1987 (Box 68, Folder 34)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Santa Rita Exchange. 1988-1991 (Box 68, Folder 35)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Service Contracts. 1991-1993 (Box 68, Folder 36)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Service Contracts. 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 37)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Sierra Vista and Enabling Act. 1983 (Box 68, Folder 38)
        - Bureau of Land Management: State Selection of Lands. 1981-1982 (Box 68, Folder 39)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Transportation Study. 1988 (Box 68, Folder 40)
        - Bureau of Land Management: USGS. 1989-1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wild Horses. 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wild Horses. 1986-1989 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wild Horses. 1988-1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wild Horses and Burros. 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wilderness. 1984-1985 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wilderness Study Guidelines. 1976-1979 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Wilderness Study Guidelines. 1980 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Withdrawal of Land. 1977-1981 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Yuma District. 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Bureau of Land Management: Yuma Mine Saguaro National Monument. 1984 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Bureau of Mines: American Mining Congress. 1988 (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Bureau of Mines: Coal Office of Technical Assessment. 1984 (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Bureau of Mines: Correspondence. 1986 (Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Bureau of Mines: Helium. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - Bureau of Mines: In Situ Copper. 1987-1994 (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - Bureau of Mines: In Situ Mining. 1985-1988 (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - Bureau of Mines: In Situ Mining. 1988 (Box 69, Folder 18)
        - Bureau of Mines: Mineral Management Service. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 19)
        - Bureau of Mines: Mineral Management Service Budget Justifications. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 20)
        - Bureau of Mines: Mineral Research Institute. 1983-1989 (Box 69, Folder 21)
        - Bureau of Mines: Mining Claims and Land Withdrawals. 1981-1984 (Box 69, Folder 22)
        - Bureau of Mines: Office of Inspector General Budget Justifications. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 23)
        - Bureau of Mines: Office of Surface Mining. 1978 (Box 69, Folder 24)
        - Bureau of Mines: Office of Surface Mining Budget Justifications. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 25)
        - Bureau of Mines: Pre-Staking on Withdrawal Lands. 1981-1982 (Box 69, Folder 26)
        - Bureau of Mines: USGS Consolidation. 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 27)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Aquifer Recharge. 1986 (Box 69, Folder 28)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Budget Hearing Material. 1981-1988 (Box 69, Folder 29)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Bullhead City Water Study. 1993 (Box 69, Folder 30)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Central Valley Project Association. 1989 (Box 69, Folder 31)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Colorado River Bridge Environmental Impact Statement. 1993 (Box 69, Folder 32)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Colorado River Flooding. 1983 (Box 69, Folder 33)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Colorado River Salinity Control (Yuma). 1977-1979 (Box 69, Folder 34)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Correspondence. 1978-1980 (Box 69, Folder 35)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Correspondence with Maricopa Water District. 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Dams and Safety. 1984-1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Equitable Life. 1984 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Glen Canyon Dam Environmental Impact Study. 1992 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Hoover Dam Visitor Center. 1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Irrigation of Ineligible Lands. 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Lake Mead (Flood Control). 1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Quail Creek Dom-Dixie Power and Light. 1988 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Reclamation Projects Authorization and Adjustment Act. 1992 (Box 70, Folder 9)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Reclamation Reform Act Regulations. 1988 (Box 70, Folder 10)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Roosevelt Lake Recreation Area. 1993 (Box 70, Folder 11)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Reorganization. 1987 (Box 70, Folder 12)
        - Bureau of Reclamation: Status of Legislation. 1984-1988 (Box 70, Folder 13)